Criminal Justice, School of; Records ua640
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Dean's General Subject Files, 1962-1989; 2; 4 cubic ft.
  - Dean Donald Newman, 1977-1984 (rec); 2.45
    - Provost/Resignation of Deanship, 1983-1984 (Box 4 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 19)
    - Punch, Maurice, 1981-1982 (Box 4 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 20)
    - Redl, Fritz, 1974-1981 (Box 4 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 21)
    - Robinson, Cyril, 1977 (Box 4 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 22)
    - Robinson, Edward, 1978 (Box 4 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 23)
    - Rockefeller College - Executive Committee Meetings, 1981 (Box 4 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 24)
    - Rosenbaum Larry, 1975-1985 (Box 4 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 25)
    - Rubin, H. Ted, 1978-1979 (Box 4 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 26)
    - Rucinski, Lady R., 1979 (Box 4 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 27)
    - Rutgers, State University of N.J., 1980 (Box 4 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 28)
    - Ryan, Edward, 1982 (Box 4 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 29)
    - Salas, Luis, 1979-1982 (Box 4 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 30)
    - SCJ Alumni Directory, 1977 (Box 4 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 31)
    - SCJ Students, 1980 (Box 4 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 32)
    - Sexual Harassment, 1980 October (Box 4 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 33)
    - School Plans, 1981 (Box 4 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 34)
    - Sherman, Lawrence, 1977-1983 (Box 4 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 35)
    - Shoham, Shlomo, 1977 (Box 4 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 36)
    - Smith, Beverly Ann, 1979-1983 (Box 4 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 37)
    - Smith, Christopher J., 1981 (Box 4 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 38)
    - Smith, Dwight, 1980; 2 folders (Box 4 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 39-40)
    - Southern Vermont College, Bennington Vt. - Dean William Glasser, 1981 (Box 4 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 41)
    - Student Association, 1979 May 15 (Box 4 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 42)
    - SUNY Press, 1980-1983; 3 folders (Box 4 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 43-45)
    - Teaching Assistants, 1980 (Box 4 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 46)
    - Tenure and Promotion, 1980-1982 (Box 4 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 47)
    - Toch, Hans, 1969-1981 (Box 4 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 48)
    - Under Cover, 1980-1981 (Box 4 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 49)
    - University Faculty Salaries, 1971-1981 (Box 4 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 50)
    - Validation Project, 1979 (Box 4 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 51)
    - Van Den Haag, Ernest, 1978-1983 (Box 4 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 52)
    - Vandervort, Lucinda A., 1980-1983 (Box 4 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 53)
    - Walker, Samuel, 1979 (Box 4 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 54)
    - Waller, Irvin, 1979-1982 (Box 4 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 55)
    - Warren, Marguerite, 1973-1983 (Box 4 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 56)
    - Watson, James, 1980 (Box 4 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 57)
    - Weinberg, Martin S., 1960-1981 (Box 4 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 58)
    - Wilbanks, Bill, 1972-1983 (Box 4 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 59)
    - Wilkins, Leslie, 1968-1983 (Box 4 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 60)
    - Wilkins, Leslie Awards Committee, 1980-1982 (Box 4 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 61)
    - Wisconsin, Univ. of, at Milwaukee, Evaluation, 1984 (Box 4 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 62)
    - Witt, James, 1977-1980 (Box 4 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 63)
    - Wolfgang, Marvin E., 1978-1983 (Box 4 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 64)
    - Zalman, Marvin, 1977-1983 (Box 4 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 65)
- Publications, 1970-1986; 3; 0.50 cubic ft.
  The publications series contains publications written by members of the faculty under the imprint of the School of Criminal Justice, and studies published under the auspices of the School of Criminal Justice. For the School of Criminal Justice Alumni News (1975-1983), the School of Criminal Justice News and Notes (1967-1975), School of Criminal Justice Graduate Bulletin (1968-1970, 1978-1981) and the School of Criminal Justice Report (1984), see the University Archives Publication File.
  - Attitudes of New York Legislators toward Crime and Criminal Justice: A Report of the State Legislature Survey, 1985-1986 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 1)
  - The County Jail: Feasible Reform in a Tight Economy, 1972 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 2)
  - Hispanic Americans and the Criminal Justice Process: A Selected Bibliography, 1980 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 3)
  - Methadone Maintenance: Problems of Evaluation, 1973 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 4)
  - The New York City Police Department Anti-Corruption Campaign, October 1970-August 1972, ca. 1972 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 5)
  - New York State Police Opinion Survey. Reducing Avoidable Case Attrition, 1986 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 6)
  - Offenses Known in New York State, 1960-1970, Vols. 1-3, ca. 1970 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 7)
  - Order and Justice on Campus, 1971 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 8)
  - Project on History: Development of Substantive Criminal Codes, 1975 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 9)
  - (Research Prospectus) A Study on the Impact of Disproportionate Imprisonment of Blacks in Contemporary American Society, 1981 (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 10)
  - Task Force Report on Police, 1972; 2 folders (Box 1 (3-Publications), Folder 11-12)
- Student Handbooks, 1970-1971; 1988-1989; 4; 0.50 cubic ft.
  The handbooks series contains the student handbooks for the School of Criminal Justice for the years listed above.
  - Student Handbook, 1970-1971 (Box 1 (4-Student Handbooks), Folder 1)
  - Student Handbook, 1971-1972 (Box 1 (4-Student Handbooks), Folder 2)
  - Student Handbook, 1972-1973 (Box 1 (4-Student Handbooks), Folder 3)
  - Student Handbook, 1973-1974 (Box 1 (4-Student Handbooks), Folder 4)
  - Student Handbook, 1974-1975 (Box 1 (4-Student Handbooks), Folder 5)
  - Student Handbook, 1975-1976 (Box 1 (4-Student Handbooks), Folder 6)
  - Student Handbook, 1976-1977 (Box 1 (4-Student Handbooks), Folder 7)
  - Student Handbook, 1977-1978 (Box 1 (4-Student Handbooks), Folder 8)
  - Student Handbook, 1979-1980 (Box 1 (4-Student Handbooks), Folder 9)
  - Student Handbook, 1981-1982 (Box 1 (4-Student Handbooks), Folder 10)
  - Student Handbook, 1982-1983 (Box 1 (4-Student Handbooks), Folder 11)
  - Student Handbook, 1983-1984 (Box 1 (4-Student Handbooks), Folder 12)
  - Student Handbook, 1984-1985 (Box 1 (4-Student Handbooks), Folder 13)
  - Student Handbook, 1985-1986 (Box 1 (4-Student Handbooks), Folder 14)
  - Student Handbook, 1986-1987 (Box 1 (4-Student Handbooks), Folder 15)
  - Student Handbook, 1988-1989 (Box 1 (4-Student Handbooks), Folder 16)
- Center on Minorities and Criminal Justice, 1977-1981; 5; 1 cubic foot
  This series contains the correspondence and publications of the Center on Minorities and Criminal Justice. Also contained in this series is a small amount of correspondence relating to the Center's predecessor, the Training Program in Criminal Justice Education. Planning and Budgetary documents as well as publications produced by the Center comprise the vast majority of the documents of this unit of the School of Criminal Justice.
  - Advisory Committee, ca. 1977 (Box 1 (5-Center on Minorities and Criminal Justice), Folder 1)
  - American Justice Center, 1981 (Box 1 (5-Center on Minorities and Criminal Justice), Folder 2)
  - Annotated Bibliography, Undated (Box 1 (5-Center on Minorities and Criminal Justice), Folder 3)
  - Asian-Americans and Crime: An Annotated Bibliography, 1981 (Box 1 (5-Center on Minorities and Criminal Justice), Folder 4)
  - Black Crime: An Annotated Bibliography, 1980 (Box 1 (5-Center on Minorities and Criminal Justice), Folder 5)
  - The Black Incarceration in the U.S.: A Nationwide Problem, 1980 (Box 1 (5-Center on Minorities and Criminal Justice), Folder 6)
  - Budget, 1978-1979 (Box 1 (5-Center on Minorities and Criminal Justice), Folder 7)
  - Budget, 1980-1981 (Box 2 (5-Center on Minorities and Criminal Justice), Folder 1)
  - Budgeting, ca. 1981 (Box 2 (5-Center on Minorities and Criminal Justice), Folder 2)
  - Clippings, 1980-1981 (Box 2 (5-Center on Minorities and Criminal Justice), Folder 3)
  - College Instructors Program, 1977-1979 (Box 2 (5-Center on Minorities and Criminal Justice), Folder 4)
  - Concept Paper: Study of Differential Incarceration Rates, Undated (Box 2 (5-Center on Minorities and Criminal Justice), Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1977-1982 (Box 2 (5-Center on Minorities and Criminal Justice), Folder 6)
  - Correspondence - Letters, 1977 (Box 2 (5-Center on Minorities and Criminal Justice), Folder 7)
  - Correspondence - Letters, 1978 (Box 2 (5-Center on Minorities and Criminal Justice), Folder 8)
  - Correspondence - Memos, 1977-1978 (Box 2 (5-Center on Minorities and Criminal Justice), Folder 9)
  - Correspondence - Memos, 1979 (Box 2 (5-Center on Minorities and Criminal Justice), Folder 10)
  - The Criminal Justice System and Minority Crime, 1980 (Box 2 (5-Center on Minorities and Criminal Justice), Folder 11)
  - The Criminal Justice System: the Extent of Minority Crime and Victimization; the Components of the Criminal Justice System, ..., Undated (Box 2 (5-Center on Minorities and Criminal Justice), Folder 12)
  - Criminology, Undated (Box 2 (5-Center on Minorities and Criminal Justice), Folder 13)
  - Education Project in Criminal Justice, 1978 (Box 2 (5-Center on Minorities and Criminal Justice), Folder 14)
  - Eight Undergraduate Courses in Criminal Justice with Emphasis on Minorities, Undated (Box 2 (5-Center on Minorities and Criminal Justice), Folder 15)
  - Establishment of the Center on Minorities and Criminal Justice, 1980 (Box 2 (5-Center on Minorities and Criminal Justice), Folder 16)
  - Hispanic Americans and Crime: An Annotated Bibliography, 1980 (Box 2 (5-Center on Minorities and Criminal Justice), Folder 17)
  - The Hispanic Inmate in U.S. Jails and Prisons: A Partial Bibliography, Undated (Box 2 (5-Center on Minorities and Criminal Justice), Folder 18)
  - Hispanic Employment Correspondence, 1980 (Box 2 (5-Center on Minorities and Criminal Justice), Folder 19)
  - Index to Minorities and Criminal Justice - Advertising, 1981 (Box 2 (5-Center on Minorities and Criminal Justice), Folder 20)
  - Index to Minorities and Criminal Justice - Distribution Correspondence, 1981 (Box 2 (5-Center on Minorities and Criminal Justice), Folder 21)
  - Index to Minorities and Criminal Justice - Outline/Periodicals List, ca. 1981 (Box 2 (5-Center on Minorities and Criminal Justice), Folder 22)
  - Index to Minorities and Criminal Justice - Correspondence - Replies, 1981 (Box 2 (5-Center on Minorities and Criminal Justice), Folder 23)
  - Judicial Procedure and Substantive Criminal Law, Undated (Box 2 (5-Center on Minorities and Criminal Justice), Folder 24)
  - Judicial Process (Course Outline), Undated (Box 2 (5-Center on Minorities and Criminal Justice), Folder 25)
  - Juvenile Delinquency, Undated (Box 2 (5-Center on Minorities and Criminal Justice), Folder 26)
  - Minorities and Civil Disturbances in the U.S.: An Annotated Bibliography, Undated (Box 2 (5-Center on Minorities and Criminal Justice), Folder 27)
  - Minorities and the Criminal Justice Process: A Selected Bibliography, Undated (Box 2 (5-Center on Minorities and Criminal Justice), Folder 28)
  - Minority Fellowships, 1978-1979 (Box 2 (5-Center on Minorities and Criminal Justice), Folder 29)
  - Monograph Series, 1979 (Box 2 (5-Center on Minorities and Criminal Justice), Folder 30)
  - National Curriculum Evaluation Panel, 1978-1979 (Box 2 (5-Center on Minorities and Criminal Justice), Folder 31)
  - Native Americans and Crime: An Annotated Bibliography, 1981 (Box 2 (5-Center on Minorities and Criminal Justice), Folder 32)
  - Our Black Prisons, 1980 (Box 2 (5-Center on Minorities and Criminal Justice), Folder 33)
  - Personnel, 1979-1980 (Box 2 (5-Center on Minorities and Criminal Justice), Folder 34)
  - Preparing Criminal Justice Undergraduate Students for a Field Experience in a Criminal Justice Agency, Undated (Box 2 (5-Center on Minorities and Criminal Justice), Folder 35)
  - Program and Budget Narrative, Undated (Box 2 (5-Center on Minorities and Criminal Justice), Folder 36)
  - Progress Reports, 1977-1981 (Box 2 (5-Center on Minorities and Criminal Justice), Folder 37)
  - Proposed Undergraduate Policing Course, 1979 (Box 2 (5-Center on Minorities and Criminal Justice), Folder 38)
  - Sales Correspondence, 1981 (Box 2 (5-Center on Minorities and Criminal Justice), Folder 39)
  - Sales Records, 1981 (Box 2 (5-Center on Minorities and Criminal Justice), Folder 40)
  - Staff Meeting Minutes, 1977-1978 (Box 2 (5-Center on Minorities and Criminal Justice), Folder 41)
  - Summer Course Materials, 1980 (Box 2 (5-Center on Minorities and Criminal Justice), Folder 42)
  - Symposium on the "Dangerous Patient", 1974 (Box 2 (5-Center on Minorities and Criminal Justice), Folder 43)
  - Training Program in Criminal Justice Education, Undated (Box 2 (5-Center on Minorities and Criminal Justice), Folder 44)
  - Vitas, Undated (Box 2 (5-Center on Minorities and Criminal Justice), Folder 45)
  - W.R.I. Corporate Capabilities Statement, 1981 (Box 2 (5-Center on Minorities and Criminal Justice), Folder 46)
  - Writings, Miscellaneous, Undated (Box 2 (5-Center on Minorities and Criminal Justice), Folder 47)